rockcitytimes.com 2015-06-15

# Privacy Policy | Rock City Times

We use third party vendors that use cookies to display advertising on this site including Google. Honestly we have no clue what all information they collect on you but they probably somehow know your mom’s name, your date of birth, your race, your 5th grade girlfriend, and where you hid the bodies. They do not however share any of that information with us or we would probably turn you into the cops for reward money.

We do know that Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Especially chocolate chip. We love to eat them, will you please give them to us? We made a [little movie expressing our desire to have your cookies](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-qTIGg3I5y8). Ok, so we didn’t really make that video, we are not that cool.

Oh, you mean the internet kind. Again we do not directly use those but our third parties, again through Google, frequently do. We utilize Google analytics in addition to advertising tracking so that we can better understand why in the hell you read our crazy content in the first place.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

No, we prefer inside parties. Plus we really have no information to disclose other than general traffic information.

**Third party links**

We link to things all the time. It is sort of our thing. If you click a link from our website you are on your own and we cannot and will not help you after that point.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

California is wonderful state that has a special place in our heart. Unfortunately they are a little picky when it comes to internet privacy so we have to throw in this line real quick:

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

In general we try to write content that makes no sense to anyone under the age of 13 (or over for that matter). Since we do not collect any information though we are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy, and leaving us your entire wealth when you die. Just kidding about that last part, but you can if you want to.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we change our privacy policy it will be a miracle. Chances are after we write this we will never look at this page again, and neither will you. In the rare event of a sudden need to hire lawyers, zombie attacks, or a grammatical issue that people complain about we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 2/7/2014
